Finding Aid for the Albert Lewin Papers PASC.0314
UCLA Library Special Collections
Albert Lewin papers
1938-1991
UCLA Library Special Collections
Lewin, Albert E. (Albert Elmar)
PASC.0314
30.5 Linear Feet (55 boxes and 7 shoe boxes)
Albert E. Lewin was a comedy writer whose career spanned from the 1930s to the 1990s. His numerous credits include a mixture of productions from radio, television, motion pictures, and stage. The collection consists of script and production files as well as small amount of business files, correspondence, sound recordings and printed material related to his career.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Audio materials in this collection are restricted and require advance notice for use.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9960923663606533
Biography
Albert E. Lewin was born on July 29, 1916 in New York City, New York. Lewin attended the Art Institute of Chicago and Los Angeles Valley College. He developed an early interest in comedy writing working as a cartoonist and comic artist for Colliers, Satevepost, and other magazines. He began writing for radio in 1938, writing jokes for Billy House's Wrigley Laughliner on the Columbia network. He contributed to radio programs working with a variety of talent including Don Ameche, Edgar Bergen and Charlie McCarthy, Bing Crosby, Victor Borge, Tommy Riggs, Judy Canova, Ransom Sherman, Charles Ruggles, Carmen Miranda, Greer Garson, and Martha Raye among others. During World War II, Lewin served in the military and fought in France and Germany for five and a half months. He then served with the American Forces Network of the Armed Forces Radio Service where he wrote and directed programs with Mickey Rooney, Jack Benny, and Bob Hope. Following the war he continued working in radio contributing to shows such as The Eddie Cantor Show, The Chase and Sanborn Program, Scattergood Baines, and The Tommy Riggs Show, among others.
He had a prolific writing career for television including credits for the series Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre, The Brady Bunch, Diff'rent Strokes, Eddie Cantor Comedy Theatre, The Ghost and Mrs. Muir, The Good Guys, My Favorite Martian, and The Odd Couple, among others. Additionally, he was involved in made for TV movie productions including Coffee, Tea, or Me. His motion picture credits include Eight on the Lam, Alice in Wonderland, Wicked Dreams of Paula Schultz, I Will, I Will...For Now, and Boy, Did I Get a Wrong Number!, among others. Lewin also co-wrote two books including The Glass Bed and two plays including The Gift Horse. He often collaborated with Norman Panama and Burt Styler on writing projects. Albert E. Lewin died of congestive heart failure in Los Angeles, CA, on April 23, 1996, he was 79.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of materials documenting the career of comedy writer, Albert E. Lewin. Included in the collection are writings for radio, television, motion pictures, and stage projects as well as a book project in which Lewin was involved. Additionally, there is a small amount of business files, correspondence, sound recordings, printed material, and memorabilia from the 63rd Infantry Division, Lewin's former Army unit. The radio related writings include a mixture of complete and partial scripts, sketches, segments, and ideas for radio programs, such as the Armed Forces Radio Servic e productions featuring Bing Crosby and Edgar Bergen, The Chase and Sanborn Program, Play Broadcast, Scattergood Baines, and The Tommy Riggs Show, among others. The writings for motion picture projects include scripts along with a small quantity of production information for produced and unproduced film projects such as Alice in Wonderland, and I Will, I Will...For Now, among others. Of particular note are writings documenting Lewin's association with Bob Hope, including Boy, Did I Get a Wrong Number!, Eight on the Lam, and I'll Take Sweden. The book project writings contain files for The Glass Bed, a novel that was adapted from an unproduced motion picture screenplay by Lewin and Norman Panama titled Hollywood and Vine.
The television writings include a mixture of complete and partial scripts, notes, story ideas, monologues, outlines, treatments, and occasional production information for television features and episodic series such as Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre, The Brady Bunch, Diff'rent Strokes, The Eddie Cantor Comedy Theatre, Facts of Life, The Ghost an Mrs. Muir, and My Favorite Martian, among others. The stage projects' writings include a mixture of complete and partial play scripts, notes, and ideas for The Gift Horse and Trashman. Additionally, there is a small portion of unidentified writings believed related to motion picture, radio, television, or other projects for which the production status and Lewin's involvement are unknown and a gag file containing handwritten jokes or one-liners compiled and possibly written by Lewin.
Also included in the collection is a very small amount of fragmentary records documenting business dealings related to Lewin's career as well as small quantity of correspondence. There are a small number of home recorded cassette tapes and audio reels of meetings and/or phone conversations created by Lewin and related to a various projects in which he was involved. There are also press clippings mentioning Lewin or the projects he was involved. Additionally, the collection contains a small number of items relating to Lewin's service in the 63rd Infantry Division. Along with Lewin's papers are a holograph manuscript of a publication titled Little Billy Boat and a press clipping related to his wife, Esther Lewin.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Radio projects
Motion picture projects
Television projects
Stage productions
Gag files
Book projects
Unidentified projects
Business files
Correspondence
Printed materials
Sound recordings
63rd Infantry Division service
Esther Lewin papers
Radio comedy writers -- United States -- Archives.; Television comedy writers -- United States -- Archives.; Lewin, Albert E. (Albert Elmar)--Archives.
- Series 1. Radio Projects, (ca. 1938-1945); Boxes 28-37
  Scope and Contents note
  The Radio Projects series includes script materials for produced and what may be unproduced radio projects in which Lewin was involved in some capacity. The series is arranged alphabetically into subseries by known radio program or project titles. For unidentified radio material, the proccessor created the subseries, Unidentified Projects. The writings include a mixture of complete and partial scripts, sketches, segments, and ideas for radio programs, such as Armed Forces Radio Service productions featuring Bing Crosby and Edgar Bergen, among others, The Chase and Sanborn Program, Play Broadcast, Scattergood Baines, and The Tommy Riggs Show, among others. A portion of the file titles were created and/or enhanced by the processor.
  - American Forces Network
    - Yessir, She's My Baby, (1945 Aug 3) (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Anything Goes
    - Show script, (no year Feb 15) (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Show script, (no year Feb 4) (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Show script, (no year Feb 13) (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Show script, (no year Feb 18) (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Show script, (Feb 25) (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Show script, (no year Mar 1) (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Show script, (no year Feb 22) (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Show script, (no year Feb 20) (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Show script, (no year Feb 27) (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Armed Forces Radio Service
    - Bing Crosby #65, (1944 Mar 2) (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Bing Crosby #68, (no date) (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Bob Crosby #25, (1944 Mar 5) (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Burns and Allen #26, (1944 Feb 22) (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Burns and Allen #29, (1944 Mar 14) (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Charlie McCarthy #56, (1944 Feb 27) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Charlie McCarthy #59, (1944 Mar 19) (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Command Performance #232, (1946 Jun 4) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly #54, (1944 Feb 22) (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Fibber McGee and Molly #57, (1944 Mar 14) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Fred Allen #33, (1944 Mar 5) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - G.I. Journal (The), (no date) (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Jack Benny #55, (1944 Mar 19) (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Melody Round-Up, (1943) (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Village Store #23, (1944 Feb 24) (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Village Store #26, (1944 Mar 16) (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Avalon Time
    - Kitty O'Neal spots/routines, (1938 Oct) (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Show scripts, (1938 Oct) (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Show scripts, (1938 Nov) (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Blood and Fire
    - Script, (1943-1944) (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Show script, (1943 Nov 7) (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Show script, (1944 Jan 30) (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Chase and Sanborn Program (The)
    - Bergen Zoot Suit first spot, (1942 Dec 28) (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - E Award, (1943 Jan 24) (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Script, (1943 Feb 14) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Script, (1943 Mar 21) (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Script, (1943 Apr 11) (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Script, (1943 Jan 17) (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Script, (1943 Mar 7) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Script, (1943 Feb 28) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Script, (1943 Feb 21) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Script, (1943 Mar 14) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Script, (1943 Apr 4) (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Script, (1943 Mar 28) (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Script, (1943 Feb 7) (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Script, (1943 Apr 18) (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Script, (1943 Apr 25) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Script, (1942 Dec 13) (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Colgate Show (The)
    - Judy Canova spot[s], (1943 Jul-Aug) (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Johnny Mercer Music Shop
    - Script, (1942 Dec 17) (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Kraft Music Hall (The)
    - Script, (1942 Oct 8) (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Script, (1942 Sept 24) (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Script, (1942 Oct 1) (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Victor Borge spot[s], (1942 Sept-Oct) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Musical Cook Book (The)
    - Script, (1938 Nov 21) (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Script, (no year Aug 24) (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Script, (1938 Dec 5) (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Script, (1938 Dec 12) (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Pepsodent Show (The) starring Bob Hope
    - Bob Hope material, (1941) (Box 34, Folder 20)
      General note
      Originally with file divider labeled Bob Hope Projects.
    - Script, (1941 Oct 28) (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Play Broadcast
    - Play Broadcast Anniversary Party (The), (no date) (Box 32, Folder 33)
      Originally filed in loosed bound binder. Scripts removed from binder for preservation purposes.
    - Publicity, (no year Feb 12) (Box 32, Folder 38)
      Pamphlets that talk about the show Play Broadcast.
    - Scrapbook-like script covers (2 items), (no date) (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Removed scripts for preservation purposes.
    - Script, (1940 Nov 25) (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Script, (1941 Jan 6) (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Script, (1940 Dec 30) (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Script, (1940 Dec 23) (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Script, (1940 Dec 16) (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Script, (1940 Dec 9) (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Script, (1940 Dec 2) (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Script, (1941 Jan 13) (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Script, (1940 Nov 18) (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Script, (1940 Nov 4) (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Script, (1940 Oct 28) (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Script, (1941 Jan 20) (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Script, (1940 Oct 14) (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Script, (1941 Mar 3) (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Script, (1940 Oct 7) (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Script, (1940 Sept 30) (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Script, (1940 Sept 23) (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Script, (1940 Oct 21) (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Script, (1941 Mar 24) (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Script, (1941 May 16) (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Script, (1941 May 9) (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Script, (1941 May 2) (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Script, (1941 Apr 25) (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Script, (1941 Apr 18) (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Script, (1941 Apr 11) (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Script, (1941 Feb 17) (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Script, (1941 Mar 31) (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Script, (1941 Jan 27) (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Script, (1941 Mar 17) (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Script, (1941 Mar 10) (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Script, (1940 Aug 26) (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Script, (1941 Feb 24) (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Script, (1940 Sept 16) (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Script, (1941 Feb 10) (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Script, (1941 Feb 3) (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Script, (1941 Apr 4) (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Script, (1940 Mar 25) (Box 31, Folder 13)
      Originally filed in loosed bound binder with scripts dated Feb 12 1940-May 13 1940. Scripts removed from binder for preservation purposes.
    - Script, (1940 May 13) (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Script, (1940 May 6) (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Script, (1940 Apr 22) (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Script, (1940 Sept 9) (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Script, (1940 May 20) (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Script, (1940 Apr 1) (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Script, (1940 Apr 29) (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Script, (1940 Mar 18) (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Script, (1940 Mar 11) (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Script, (1940 Mar 1) (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Script, (1940 Feb 22) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Script, (1940 Feb 19) (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Script, (1940 Feb 12) (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Script, (1940 Apr 8) (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Script, (1940 Aug 9) (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Script, (1940 Sept 2) (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Script, (1940 Apr 15) (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Script, (1940 Aug 19) (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Script, (1940 Jun 24) (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Script, (1940 Aug 5) (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Script, (1940 Nov 11) (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Script, (1940 Jul 29) (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Script, (1940 Jul 15) (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Script, (1940 Jul 8) (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Script, (1940 Jul 1) (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Script, (1940 Jun 17) (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Script, (1940 Jun 10) (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Script, (1940 Jun 3) (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Script, (1940 May 27) (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Script, (1940 Jul 22) (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Ransom Sherman Show (The)
    - Script, (1942 Apr 8) (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Script, (1942 Apr 1) (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Scattergood Baines
    - Episode One, (no date) (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Episode Two, (no date) (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Good Will Show, (1941 Jul) (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Notes for new trends on show, (1941 Oct 8) (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Pliny Goes Night-clubbing, (no date) (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Scattergood Baines Goes to the City Episode #1, (no date) (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Scattergood Baines Goes to the City Episode #2, (no date) (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Scattergood Baines in the City, (no date) (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Story ideas to relocate the show to the city in order to attract more viewers.
    - Scattergood Teaches Squire Hooper What it Means to Be a Storekeeper, (1941 Jul 18) (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Show script, (1941 Jul 11) (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Story of Scattergood Baines (The), (1941 Aug 8) (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Suggested Scattergood Baines Comic Situations for Sequence YY, (1941 Jul 21) (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Tommy Riggs Show
    - Auction (The), (no date) (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Characters, (1942 Jun 11) (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Circus Tickets, (no date) (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Department Store Commercial, (no year Sept 2) (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Filling Station Commercial, (no year Sept 2) (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - General gags, (no year Sept 2) (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Lawnmower (The), (no date) (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - New Dress (The), (no date) (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Stuffed Owl (The), (no date) (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Tommy Riggs Show (The)
    - Script, (1942 Sept 1) (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Script, (1942 Jul 28) (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Script, (1942 Jul 7) (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Script, (1942 Aug 4) (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Script, (1942 Aug 11) (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Script, (1942 Jul 21) (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Script, (1942 Jul 14) (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Script, (1942 Aug 25) (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Script, (1942 Sept 8) (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Script, (1942 Sept 15) (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Script, (1942 Aug 18) (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Script, (1942 Jun 14) (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Unidentified Project?
    - Meyerhoff - Society for the Best of a Lifetime, (1946-1947) (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Script material, remarks, and correspondence regarding what appears to be a project with Joe E. Brown, the Society For the Best of a Lifetime.
  - Unidentified Projects
    - Assorted ideas, (no date) (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Appears to be for Somerset Reads the Funnies and The Truth About You
    - Script pages and notes that appear related, (no date) (Box 36, Folder 11)
      Appears to be for radio.
    - Scripts material and outlines, (no date) (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Appears to be produced and or unproduced writings for a variety of shows written by or in collaboration with Lewin. Folder originally titled Miscellaneous Show Material.
  - Voices from Nowhere
    - Script, (no date) (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Script, (1939 Nov 26) (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Script, (1939 Oct 15) (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - War of the Worlds (Box 60)
    Scope and Content
    Orson Welles.
    Complete broadcast
- Series 2. Motion Picture Projects, (ca. 1954-1991); Boxes 34-41 and 45-53
  The Motion Picture Projects series includes script materials and a small amount of production information for produced and what appear to be unproduced film projects in which Lewin was involved in some capacity. The series is arranged into a subseries alphabetically by project titles. The script material includes a mixture of complete and partial scripts and notes. Additionally, there are occasional shooting schedules, call sheets, and letters about productions found among the files. Projects include Alice in Wonderland and I Will, I Will...For Now, among others. Of particular note are scripts documenting Lewin's association with Bob Hope, including Boy, Did I Get a Wrong Number!, Eight on the Lam, and I'll Take Sweden. Additionally, there are materials for Hollywood and Vine, an unproduced work which was later adapted into the published novel, The Glass Bed. See also Book Projects for material related to The Glass Bed.
  - Alice in Wonderland
    - Correspondence regarding Alice in Wonderland to and from Lewin and Lou Bunin., (1951 Jun) (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Letter from Lewin to Lou and Henri regarding Alice project and Disney, (1946 Nov 23) (Box 52, Folder 5)
      With two snap shots.
    - Loose script pages, (1947 Nov) (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Proposed plan, (1947 Jul 23) (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Proposed plan, (1947 Jul 29) (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Publicity and Reviews, (1947-1951) (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Rough script, (1947) (Box 52, Folder 3)
      Annotated.
    - Script, (1947 Nov) (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Script materials, (1947) (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Shooting script sequence 1 to 23, (1947 Nov) (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Shooting script sequence 24 to 38, (1947 Nov) (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Typescript pages, (no date) (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Appears to be chapters II-XI from Alice in Wonderland.
  - Beard (The) -Also known as Hollywood and Vine
    See audio work tapes in box 57
    - Script, (no date) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Boy, Did I get a Wrong Number!
    - Notes etc. (folder 1 of 2) - rewrites and notes, (1965 Aug-Oct) (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Notes etc. (folder 2 of 2) - rewrites and, (1965 Oct-Nov) (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Script, (1965 Sept 15) (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Script materials and production information, (1965 Sept-Dec) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Call Me Mister
    - Plot outline for The Cats, (1949 Oct 17) (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Publicity and Reviews, (1951) (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Script, (1950 Jun 8) (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Eight on the Lam
    - Box Office Award certificate and publicity, (1967 Jun-Jul) (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Script, (1966 Jul 16) (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Script, (1966 May-Sept) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Script, (1966 Jul 16) (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Script, (1966 Aug 19) (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Script and production information, (1966 Aug-Oct) (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Five Graves to Cairo audio tape track (Box 58)
  - Friendly Island
    - Notes and scene breakdown, (1950-1951) (Box 34, Folder 17)
      Released as Down Among the Sheltering Palms. With comments by Mr. Zanuck.
    - Screen Writers Guild writing credits, (1951) (Box 34, Folder 16)
      Released as Down Among the Sheltering Palms. With communications about Fox voluntary salary reduction.
  - Hollywood and Vine
    Work audio tapes in box 56
    - Cutting, rewrite, and casting notes, (1975, 1977) (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Master copy and notes, (no date) (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Revision work tape, 76 (Box 58)
    - Notes and rewrites, (no date) (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Original Draft, (1974) (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Rejection letters with reader reports, (1973-1991) (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Script, (1983 Nov 2) (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Script, (no date) (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Script, (1975 Nov 5) (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Script- original cut version, (1987 Aug) (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Xerox Safety of Original Typescript, (1974) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - I Don't Care
    - Script materials, (1950) (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Includes notes, correspondence, and outlines relating to the project.
  - I Will, I Will...For Now
    Work audio tapes in box 59,60
    - Assistant Directors breakdown sheet, (no date) (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Contract (The) - master script, (1971 Oct) (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Contract (The) - revised original, (no date) (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Contract (The) - rewrites and edits, (no date) (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Contract (The) - rewrites and edits, (1973) (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Also known as the Further Adventures in the Erogenous Zone.
    - Contract (The) - script, (no date) (Box 51, Folder 5)
      Appears to be an early working title for I Will, I Will...For Now. Annotated.
    - Contract (The) - script, (no date) (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Contract (The) - script, (no date) (Box 51, Folder 3)
      Appears to be an early working title for I Will, I Will...For Now.
    - Correspondence, (1986 Oct 1) (Box 48, Folder 5)
      Correspondence related to I Will, I Will...For Now.
    - Draft script, (1974 Sept 20) (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Draft script, (1975 Feb 10) (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Original shooting script changed pages, (1975 Mar-Apr) (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Production materials, (1975 Apr-Jun) (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Includes: call sheets, shooting schedules, and cast and crew sheets.
    - Production Materials, (1975) (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, (1975-1976) (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Script, (1975 Mar 3) (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Script, (1975 Mar 3) (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Script, (1975 Mar 26) (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Script pages, (1975 Mar-Apr) (Box 48, Folder 7)
      Stills from movie filed throughout.
    - Script pages, rewrites and edits (folder 1 of 2), (1975) (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Script pages, rewrites and edits (folder 2 of 2), (1975) (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Script, early revisions, (1974) (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - I'll Take Sweden